this last year we anima Carly Tufnell
humanity and it was really on that
objectives of saying you know habitat
need our programs across many many
different countries in Asia we have this
approvals concept would like to marry
the two together and in the absence of a
disaster we can click projects that you
already have an existence that we've
insufficient the volunteer the program
has been in Siem Reap province
most people know of Siem Reap the
fantastic place where the Angkor Wat
temples are and that's a real tourist
attraction we're about 30 kilometres
outside of Siem Reap in the real rural
heart back in banteay srei district and
a little community called run
technically this is a poor place this is
a hand-to-mouth existence and we've been
able to create housing for families who
basically lived in palm old pieces of
wood rubbish corrugated iron water
coming in and we've actually created a
respectable decent home for them with
sanitation and water and that's a really
great thing to see the environment we
can create a more Prudential staff come
together and doesn't matter which
project which country no no one's ever
met each other before they all come from
countries it's very easy to activate
people to get them motivating sago and
all this house will go anywhere
I was a great privilege to watch the
house
[Music]
it's just very fulfilling like going
onto the ground really doing the work
and building houses these are things
actually I don't I never get to just do
it so I never get a chance to actually
like scrap the bamboo lay a brick never
and this is the first time that actually
done it in your life
[Music]
good to see you know people from all
different part of Prudential from live
from PCA from a spring all working
together to complete a task and everyone
is enjoying it and to see that
eventually this is gonna make a
difference to the villages it gives us
the motivation I think it is really nice
coming here and it really puts into a
perspective on how different their lives
are I hope that they enjoy what we've
built for them I really hope that
particularly with the school that they
can accommodate more kids as well and
get more education
[Music]
it's not about just being there when
it's extreme it's about being the period